这么着怎么样?
Okay,
how 'bout this?
我们在一架私人飞机上
We're on a private
jet, right?
所有的乘客都睡着了
And all the passengers,
they're asleep.
我是机长
￡- Yeah.
￡- Yeah. And l'm the captain
你是空姐
and you're
the flight attendant.
好的
Okay.
你好  vicky
Hello, vicky.
等等 谁是vicky?
Wait. Who's vicky?
你啊
You are.
－ 我就不能演我自己?
－ 好吧
￡- Why can't l just be me?
￡- All right.
就演你自己
Okay, all right.
Fine, fine. You're you.
你好  Debbie
Hello, Debbie.
我一般
Boy, l...
飞行的时候不会抽筋
usually don't
cramp up when l fly,
可以的话脱了你衣服
but maybe you could
take off your clothes
帮我按摩下我的脖子
and rub my neck
a little.
等等 Ray
Okay, wait,
Ray￡-￡-
你就不能演你自己吗?
Ray, can you
just be you?
不行 我不会开飞机
l can't be me.
l don't know how to fly this thing.
忘了飞机吧
Just forget
the airplane.
我只想和你一起在床上就行
l just want to be here
in our bedroom with you.
你真变态哟
What kind of pervert
are you?
－ 哦 不
－ 怎么了
￡- Oh, no.
￡- What, what no?
门都锁了大家都睡了
Everything's locked,
turned off or asleep.
不是 我刚想起来
我的东西用完了
No, no. l just remembered,
l think l'm out of stuff.
－ 东西?
－ 是的 也许这里还有一管
￡- Stuff?
￡- Yeah. There might be a tube of it
－ 放在某处
－ 一管?
￡- around here somewhere.
￡- Tube?
一管 对 一管
除非你还想当一次父亲
A tube. Yes, a tube.
Unless you want to be a father again,
快把它找出来
￡- look for the tube.
￡- Well￡-￡-
在哪呢?长什么样?
where￡-￡- what does
it look like?
都那么久了 该过期了
lt's been so long,
it's probably expired.
快嘛 一切都那么顺利
Come on, everything
was going so well.
我在家你也醒着
l was home,
you were awake.
－ 找到了!找到了!
－ 你找到了!
￡- Got it, got it!
￡- You got it?
找到了!
Got it.
Ray这是防晒霜
￡- Yes.
￡- Ray, this is sunblock.
没问题 就当我们在海滩上
Okay. Now, we're on
a beach... right?
Yeah.
你来自上流社会
You're the rich
society￡-￡-
我叫胡安 一个穷小子
翻译: 柠檬蛋
F6 美剧总部
http://www.friends6.com/
做得真好
Nice going.
你什么意思?
What's that
supposed to mean?
我说....
l mean...
避孕药用完了
running out
of the stuff.
真棒呀!
Way to go.
那你怪我了是不是?
So, you're blaming me?
什么? 你负责买这些东西的嘛
Well, what? You're the one
who's in charge of the stuff.
为什么总是我?
Well, why do l always
have to be in charge?
你怎么不去药店买些回来
Why don't you go to the drugstore
and get some things?
东西 我不喜欢买东西回来
Things. You know
l don't like the things.
我也不喜欢买那些
Well, l don't like
the stuff.
我连买的过程都不喜欢
l don't even like
to buy the things.
特别是美女站着那里收款
Especially if there's
a lady cashier.
我觉得好下流
l feel￡-￡-
l feel all dirty.
就像再说 "嘿! 猜猜我晚上要做什么?"
Like, "Hey, hey!
Guess what l'm gonna be doing later?"
如果
Maybe.
我把孩子都哄睡的话
lf l can get all
the kids to sleep and...
月亮和星星都排成一条线...
if the moon and the stars
all line up.
还有个办法
Well, there is another
option, you know?
－ 什么?
－ 我们决定下
￡- Well, what?
￡- We discussed it.
一点点咔嚓咔嚓
￡- A little snip, snip.
￡- Hey. Hey!
天啊 不要
Ow! No!
都说些什么啊
Watch with that kind
of talk, huh?
它听的见哦!
He can hear you.
别听疯婆子说的
Don't listen
to the crazy lady, okay?
没有咔嚓咔嚓
Don't￡-￡-
no snip, snip.
不要咔嚓咔嚓
No snip, snip.
不如你告诉你...小兄弟
Why don't you
tell your... partner,
这是为它着想
that it might be
in his best interest
做点负责任的事情
to take over this
little responsibility?
它就可以经常出来透透气
He might get out
more often.
你在建议什么？
What are you saying there?
我是说
l'm just saying
如果不是我
that if l wasn't
in charge
管着所有家务活
of absolutely
everything,
理论上
l might,
theoretically,
我可能嘿咻
be more
inclined to￡-￡-
更多点
more often.
嗯
Hmm.
但是...
But...
我们真要做的太激烈的话
now if we were to do
something this drastic,
我们需要白纸黑字
we might need
something in writing.
这个...
Well...
我不可能给你做保证 但是
l can't give you
any guarantees, but￡-￡-
我...我的客户需要些担保
My￡-￡- my client is going to need
some assurances here.
我相信我们是能够达成协议的
l'm sure we can reach
a satisfying arrangement.
要不你俩先商量一下?
Why don't you two
discuss it?
下次会议我们会讨论的
Yeah, l'll bring it up
at the next meeting.
放心 我知道怎么做
Relax, l know what
l'm doing.
嗨 Ray
Hey, Ray.
万圣节快乐！
Happy Halloween.
嗨 Nemo
H￡-hey, Nemo.
纯粹为了生意
lt's good for business.
停止用你的目光脱我的衣服
And stop undressing me
with your eyes.
－ 让一下
－ 嘿嘿嘿
￡- 'Scuse me.
￡- All right, yeah. Hey. Oh, hey, huh?
欢迎来地狱 马上为你服务
Welcome to hell.
l'll be right with you.
嗨 Ray
￡- Hey, hey, Ray.
￡- Hey.
你好吗?
Yeah.
What's up?
坐下 我们在等Angelina今天穿什么
Sit down. We're waiting to see
what Angelina's wearing.
记得去年那件兔子服饰吗?
￡- Oh, yeah.
￡- Remember last year's bunny outfit?
怎么会忘 我都不会开车了
Remember?
l couldn't drive home.
嗨 我一分钟就过来
Hi, guys. l'll be
with you in one minute.
请用尺子惩罚我
Please whack me
with your ruler,
修女Mary 嗷 嗷 嗷
Sister Mary
Wowie￡-wow￡-wow￡-wow!
Andy 她会吐口水进我们的午餐的
Andy, she's gonna spit
in our food.
－ 您可以点餐了吗?
－ 当然
￡- Can l take your order?
￡- Sure.
我愿意听你指挥
And then l'd like
to join your order.
你们还是要老样子？
So, you guys want
your usual?
－ 是的 很好
－ 给我一瓶姜汁汽水
￡- Yeah, that'd be great.
￡- Just give me a ginger ale.
我得走了
￡- l gotta go.
￡- Okay.
你忙着去哪?
Where you going so fast?
我预约了医生
l got a little
doctor appointment.
你没事吧?
You okay?
我很好 只是一点
Yeah, no, l'm all right.
lt's just a￡-￡-
一点小手术
it's a little
procedure.
橡皮手套?
(一般指肛门检查)
Rubber glove, right?
不是手套
No. No glove.
他不用橡皮手套?
He doesn't use
a glove?
不是那个
lt's not that,
all right?
我就不能有点隐私?
Just￡-￡- come on.
Can l have a little privacy here?
当然 我明白
Yeah, sure, sure.
l understand.
我不明白
Well, l don't.
为什么要有隐私呢
l mean, why are we
hiding things?
我们是好朋友
We're best friends.
我向你读过我作的诗
l read you my poetry.
好吧 我去做输精管切除术
All right, l'm getting
a vasectomy.
输精管切除术?
￡- vasectomy?
￡- Mm￡-hm.
什么和切除术这词对仗呢？
What rhymes
with vasectomy?
你去做切除术?
You're getting
a vasectomy?
输精管切除术?
￡- Come on.
￡- vasectomy?
－ Raymond真勇敢啊
－ 谢谢修女
￡- very courageous, Raymond.
￡- Thank you, Sister.
从前有个人从Schenectady来(作诗状...)
There once was a man
from Schenectady, huh?
Debra同意了？
ls Debra okay
with this?
同意?她拿着剪刀跟我说的
Okay? She came
at me with a pair of scissors.
嗨Ray 我听说你要去"剪彩"去了?
Hey, Ray, l heard you
were cutting the wires.
别闹了
Oh, come on.
只想告诉这很好
l just wanna tell
you it's great.
－ 你做了?
－ 是的
￡- You had one?
￡- Oh, yeah.
你会得到很多很多爱的
You're gonna get love like
you never got love before.
他在跟我调情?
Was he flirting
with me?
来了
Here you go.
听着
All right, guys, listen.
谢谢你们关心我
￡- Thanks for your advice and all that.
￡- Ray,
Ray 让我说个词
let me just say one
word, okay?
Paplowski
Paplowski.
什么?
What?
Paplowski
Paplowski.
和我一个警队的
Guy on my squad.
我们一起毕的业
We went through
the academy together.
拥有美好的将来
Had a great future.
然后他去做了
And then he got fixed.
从此大不一样
He was never the same.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
这么说吧 自从做了以后
Well, let's just say,
after the procedure,
他那里...
he had trouble...
敬礼从此困难
saluting the captain.
－ 敬礼?
－ 对, 可以保护当事人
￡- Saluting the captain?
￡- Yeah. He could protect,
但不能保证服役了
but he could
not serve.
－ 真的?
－ 真的
￡- Really?
￡- Yeah.
把人都搞废了知道不?
Completely messed up
his head, you know?
永远不能原谅自己在打空炮
Never got over the fact
that he was firing blanks.
最后一次见他
他在商场里当保安了
Last time l saw the guy
he was working security at the mall.
可怜的家伙
The poor bastard.
我不想在商场工作
l don't wanna work
at the mall.
只是让你再想想
Just thought l'd give you
something to think about.
我俩得再开一次会
We're gonna have to have
another meeting.
你回来啦
Oh, you're back.
Ray 我觉得对不起你
Oh, Ray.
l feel terrible.
我应该陪你去看医生
l wish you would've let
me go to the doctor with you.
你还好吧?
Are you okay, hmm?
我很好
￡- l'm fine.
￡- Oh, Ray.
可能会疼一久
Gonna be sore for
a little while.
－ 别闹了
－ 我没做
￡- No, come on.
￡- l didn't do it.
为什么?
￡- Why not, what happened?
￡- Well...
－ 去做有风险
－ 有吗?
￡- there are some risks.
￡- There are?
对 我在Nemo店里跟兄弟们说
Yeah, l was talking
to the guys at Nemo's￡-￡-
Nemo店里的兄弟们
￡- Oh, the guys at Nemo's.
￡- Well￡-￡-
想得真妙
Brilliant medical minds.
怎么给你预约的?
How did you get
an appointment?
我决定不自残了
All right, look,
l changed my mind about
但是
mutilating myself,
but...
我也不是个孬种
l'm not a complete
coward.
给你
￡- There you go.
￡- What?
什么?
Yeah.
这不是...
Are these￡-￡-
东西
Things.
我买东西了
l got the things.
你买了!
You did!
这些就是东西了?
￡- Uh￡-huh.
￡- These are things?
哇! 颜色怎么那么花哨啊
Whoo! What's with all
the fancy colors?
万圣节嘛! 它也要穿件小衣服
Well, it's Halloween.
He wants to dress up too.
真不敢相信你买了
Wow! l can't believe
that you bought these.
我跟美女说
l told the lady￡-￡-
l said,
"把那七彩包给我
"Hey give me
the rainbow pack, lady.
你知道我要做什么!"
And whatever you're thinking,
that's right!
对头!
Yeah!
我会经常来买的
And l'm going to be
a regular here,
别忘了进货"
so just keep
the tab open."
－ 你真说了?
－ 是的
￡- You didn't say that.
￡- l did.
我还打了存货员一拳
l said that and then
l punched out a stock￡-boy
然后把商品架也踢翻了
and kicked over
the Sucrets rack.
我为你自豪
Well, l'm proud
of you.
你给我听好 甜妹子
And you listen up here,
sweet sister.
从今往后
From now on, all this?
This is￡-￡-
我全权负责
it's all my
responsibility, okay?
你再也不用想了
You don't think about it.
Not at all.
我负责买
Okay? l do it all.
我撕你的票 带你入座
l take your ticket,
l show you to your seat.
一站式服务
￡- Yeah, yeah?
￡- lt's all me.
你只管放松
Yeah. So you just,
you know, clear your mind...
安排好时间
￡- Mm￡-hm?
￡- and your schedule
然后给大力水手菠菜吃
and give Popeye
some spinach.
没问题 等"不请吃就捣蛋"完了
(万圣节儿童游戏)
Mm, you got it.
Right after trick￡-or-treating.
孩子们都睡了
And the kids fall asleep.
我在想是不是 9:30开始
But, l'm thinking it
could all happen by 9:30.
行没问题
￡- Yeah? All right.
￡- Yeah.
因为体育节目10:00
￡- And then Sports Center at 10:00.
￡- Well￡-￡-
我可能10:00还没结束你
well, l might not be done
with you by 10:00.
那9:15开始?
Well, could we start
at 9:1 5?
因为我真的想看...
'Cause l really want
to watch￡-￡-
妈咪我等着穿翅膀
￡- Mommy, l'm ready for my wings.
￡- Hey!
Ally 我的小天使
Ally, my little
angel girl.
我们来穿上翅膀
Okay, come on.
Let's go put your wings on, okay?
瞧见没
See?
一买东西
Every time you buy
the things,
梦想就成真
another angel
gets her wings.
是不
Come on.
一起说:虫 牙
Everybody say cavities.
虫 牙!
Cavities!
科学怪人!
Frankenstein!
饿了!
Hungry!
吃小孩!
Eat...
children!
爸 每年都一样的装束?
Come on, Dad.
Every year the same thing?
上面螺钉都生修了
Your bolts are rusting.
Frank? Frank
Frank? Frank.
Frank
Frank.
把糖还我
Give me￡-￡-
give me back the candy￡-￡-
我需要
l need them.
是给小孩子的
Now l mean it.
lt's for the children!
我糖不够发了
Please, come on, l don't
have enough candy.
别装傻了
Stop being foolish.
我糖不够发了
l￡-￡- l don't have
enough candy!
你以为你不像平时?
You think that's so different
from who you really are?
博士做了个破新娘
Doctor make bad bride!
科学怪人要告博士!
Frankenstein sue doctor!
出门了 出门了
Okay, come on, let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
嗨 Frank
Hey, Frank.
帽子是什么?
What's with the hat?
我是个空姐
l'm a stewardess.
有机会先登机吗?
Any￡-￡- any chance
of pre￡-boarding?
9:30 游戏完了
9:30, after
trick￡-or-treating.
走了 去要十家糖果就回来
All right. Come on, guys.
10 houses and out!
Frank 你留守
Yeah, thanks for holding
down the fort, Frank.
成人频道你还有没有?
Hey, you still got
the naked channel?
是的 但看不清楚
Yeah, but it's all
scrambled.
我不介意
l don't mind.
－你的装束呢?
－这就是
￡- Where's your costume?
￡- This is it.
我是个不能等到9:30的人
l'm going as the guy
who can't wait for 9:30.
不给糖就捣蛋!
Trick or treat!
吓死我了!
He scared me!
没事
lt's okay.
吓小孩很好玩吗?
What is wrong with you,
scaring children like that?
对不起
l'm sorry.
l'm very sorry.
我一点都不可怕
Look, look.
l'm not scary! See?
吓死我了!
He scared me!
要糖吃吗?
我有很多糖
Okay, you like candy?
l got lots of candy.
来 给你
Here, here.
Here we go.
你的 你的
Here you go.
There you go. There you go.
－ 我也要!
－ 这是你的糖
￡- l want some!
￡- You get some candy, too. There you go.
别对着我家扔厕纸
There you go. Okay, don't toilet
paper the house, okay?
我儿子是警察哦!
My son's a cop!
Boo!
哇 不少糖果了?
￡- Wow, that's a lot of candy, huh?
￡- Yeah!
－ 今晚该够了
－ 没有 没有
￡- That should be enough for tonight.
￡- No. No!
我们才去了四家 快点
Honey, we've only been
to four houses, come on.
好吧
All right! Come on,
come on, come on.
不给糖就捣蛋!
Trick or treat!
不好意思 科学怪人的烂牙店打烊了.
Sorry, Frankenstein's
House of Tooth Decay is closed.
噢........
Aww.
有什么办法?
Well, what can l say?
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
Here, here.
给你
There you go.
科学怪人真没劲!
Frankenstein sucks.
Frankenstein
sucks!
科学怪人真没劲!
Frankenstein sucks!
Frankenstein
sucks!
科学怪人真有劲!
Frankenstein no suck.
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
糖果 糖果
Candy, candy, candy.
嗯
Hm.
有货了!
Here we go!
不给糖就捣蛋
￡- Trick or treat.
￡- Trick or treat!
亲爱的
Sweet dears.
你们糟透了
You look terrible.
你像盒蛋糕
You look like a cupcake.
谢谢 快进来
Thank you.
Come on in.
Marie 我们得走了 得把孩子都放回床上
You know, Marie, we really gotta go,
'cause we gotta put the kids down.
放在这吧 亲爱的
他们可以在这过夜
Put 'em down here, honey.
They could spend the night.
－ 妈咪行吗?
－ 不行亲爱的 Marie我们....
￡- Could we, Mommy?
￡- No, honey. Marie, we really￡-￡-
这是好注意
That's a great idea, Ma.
No, that's good!
孩子们都想在这过夜是不?
You kids, you wanna
spend the night, right?
－ 看吧?
－ 奶奶家吗? 是
￡- Yes. See there?
￡- With Grandma? Yeah.
－ 奶奶有很多糖果哦
－ 好也
￡- Grandma's got lots of candy.
￡- Yeah!
进来进来
Come on.
这儿呢
Here, here,
look.
快去追
Go get it,
go get it.
－ 真聪明啊
－ 对 先生们女士们
￡- That's very clever.
￡- Yes. Ladies and gentlemen,
指挥塔允许起飞
欢迎乘坐本次航班
we have clearance from the tower.
Please, enjoy your flight!
你来的真及时
You made it
just in time, kid.
最后一个了
The last one.
我差点自己吃了
l almost ate it
myself.
谢谢科学怪人
Thanks,
Frankenstein.
嘿 是吸血鬼
Hey, it's Dracula.
－ 嗨 Dad
－  Frank
￡- Hey, Dad.
￡- Hey, Frank.
孩子们呢？
Where are the kids?
他们在你家过夜
Oh, they're going
to spend the night at your house.
知不知道你没留够糖果
You know, you didn't
leave me enough candy.
真的?满满一碗啊
Really? 'Cause that
bowl was full.
没糖差点造成骚乱了
l almost had a riot
on my hands.
还好橱柜里有巧克力币
Good thing l found those chocolate coins
you left in the cupboard.
巧克力币?
Chocolate coins?
巧克力币
Chocolate coins
用漂亮的包装纸包着的 Ray
in brightly
colored wrappers, Ray.
那些东西?
The things?
你把那些东西发出去了?
￡- You gave out the things?
￡- Yeah.
是的 那有怎么样?
Yeah, so what?
怎么样?
So?!
你不能进别人屋
You don't go
into somebody's house
随便拿人家橱柜里的东西
and go in their cabinets
and take their things
发给小孩子 你这疯子!
and give 'em out,
you maniac!
万圣节
lt's Halloween.
小孩要糖吃你都得给!
You gotta give the kids
what they want!
怎么了?
What's going
on here?
人家投诉我们家发出去的糖果
l'm getting complaints
about the treats coming from this house.
天啊!
Oh my God.
Ray 看来我们得搬家了
Ray, the neighbors!
We're gonna have to move now.
你留着糖自己庆贺?
What, what? Were you saving
them for something?
是!
Yes!
是留给自己庆贺用的!
￡- As a matter of fact, yes!
￡- All right, Ray.
东西啊, Debra
我们没东西了
The things, Debra.
We have no more things!
吸血鬼!
Dracula!
吸血鬼!!
Dracula!!
我不明白 有什么大不了的?
l don't get it.
What's the big deal?
有什么大不了的?
What's the big
deal?
你 真 变 态.
You are sick.
非常非常抱歉 简
And again, we are very
sorry, Jean.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
不是
lt was not￡-￡-
no￡-￡-
这不是政治声明
it was not a political
statement.
是我家
Well, it's just￡-￡-
it was just my...
老爸
father￡-in￡-law.
对不起
Yeah, and l'm sorry.
很对不起
Believe me,
l'm sorry.
好的 再见
Okay, bye￡-bye.
先别睡
Don't go to sleep,
don't go to sleep.
－ 到手了
－ 你要回来了?
￡- Got it.
￡- You got it?
要回来了
Got it, got it,
got it.
我不得不找了15家的吸血鬼
l had to go through
1 5 Draculas
才找到拿着"东西"的小孩
until l found
the right one.
然后我跟他买糖果
And then l bought
it off him.
他不知道他手上拿着什么?
Did he know what he had?
不 为了不引起怀疑
No, but l didn't want
to get him suspicious,
所以我还向他买了爆米花
so l also bought
a popcorn ball,
果浆软糖和一盒葡萄干
a marshmallow ghost
and a box of raisins.
你知道我向多少家道歉了?
Do you know how many parents
l've had to talk to tonight?
如果超过两打
Well, if it's more
than two dozen,
就不是我们一家发"东西"了
then we're not the only ones
giving out the things.
别人会认为...天啊
No, now people are gonna
think￡-￡- oh God.
我们
￡- What?
￡- That we're...
正在...
having...
疯狂嘿咻
wild sex.
这个...
Well...
他们如果一直那么想
as long as they're
gonna think it.
你怎么还有心思?
How can you
still want to?
来嘛!
￡- Hey, hey.
￡- Come on.
想想我们都付出那么多了
Whoa, whoa. Let's￡-￡- let's remember
why we did all this, huh?
我知道这令人心烦
Look, l know it's easy
to get distracted
路上困难不少
by all these little
distractions here, but...
但我们必须努力奋斗
we gotta keep our eye
on the prize, there.
我有个梦想
l have a dream!
对嘛
There.
这是个微笑
There's the smile.
这是个热吻
There's the kiss.
好吧
All right.
这是我的客户
￡- There's my client.
￡- Oh.
－噢 不
－怎么了?
￡- Oh, no.
￡- What's the matter?
巧克力?!
Chocolate?!
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat.
嘿! 胡克船长!
Hey!
Captain Hook!
你从科学怪人那儿要过糖果吗?
Did you get any candy
from Frankenstein?
不 不 别睡下
No, no, honey.
Come on, stay awake. Stay awake.
对嘛 睁开眼睛
Get up. That's it.
Bright eyed.
别睡下
Come on, bushy tailed,
let's go.
不 不 别睡下 我们唱歌吧
No, no, stay awake.
Let's sing.
& 约翰 杰克布
金格尔荷曼 史米特! &
& John Jacob
Jingleheimer Schmidt! &
嘿! 说你呢! 尼克松!
Hey, you￡-￡- Nixon!
你从科学怪人那儿要过糖果吗?
Did you get any candy
from Frankenstein?
嘿!
Hey!
我知道你住哪儿 鬼马小精灵!
l know where
you live, Casper!
不要啊! 亲爱的!
No, no, no!
No, honey, come on. Come on.
我恨万圣节!
l hate Halloween!
不管了 体育时间!
Eh, Sports Center.
欢迎观看! 本集完